[English subtitles are available]
[Song of the Moon]
[Episode 10]
Liu Shao.
Lu Li.
Lu Li, where are you?
Lu Li?
Isn't this my home?
Why am I back?
It's you?
You changed my fate after I turned 18?
That's right.
It was me.
I met the great demon
and then hid in Marquis Wuyang's Mansion.
What an exciting life!
But
I still have to thank you
for letting me meet Lu Li.
Really?
You're not him anymore.
I am him.
If you don't believe me,
you can see for yourself.
One has compassion for the universe
while the other is a scourge to the three realms.
You are not him.
They are…
Lu Li.
Do you see?
It's me.
She's destined to kill you.
Liu Shao.
How could this happen?
Wait.
This is an illusion.
Lu Li?
This must be an illusion.
What's going on?
How could this happen?
That's right.
Are they in danger?
Liu Shao.
I trust you.
You…
Can you get away?
This is all an illusion.
I have to get out.
Brother.
Brother, how is it?
How is it?
How are you feeling?
Are you all right?
Who was the one
who broke through the illusion
and completed the trial?
Was it me?
But I didn't do anything.
Lu Li, wasn't it you?
It wasn't me.
It was you.
From the Spirit Fire to King Herb,
and then to the Moon Sword,
it's been proven
that you're the right one to draw the sword.
In that case,
Liu Shao will draw the sword.
You will inherit the title of Marquis Wuyang.
-Lu Li. -That's impossible.
Lu Li is the current Marquis Wuyang?
My Lord, well...
He who knows others is smart.
He who knows himself is wise.
He who overcomes others is powerful.
He who disciples himself is invincible.
I trust you.
Thank you, my Lord.
I'll give you half of the King Herb.
But my Lord,
don't you need this to renew your life?
It's far better to renew the future of the world
than renew my life alone.
I'll accept the order.
I wish
the King Herb
can help Liu Shao
increase her spiritual power
to pull out the Moon Sword.
From then on, the human world
will only kneel to our parents,
no longer
held by other races.
I'll accept the order.
To pacify the demons and protect all beings!
My Lord.
The two disciples of Marquis Wuyang
have come out from the Moon Platform.
I heard the female disciple
passed the Moon Sword Trial.
That means
she might really be able to pull out the Moon Sword.
She's good, brother.
Tell me.
What's her name again?
Liu Shao?
It seems that the three worlds
will never be peaceful again.
There has never been peace
in the three worlds.
Its chaos
is not bad for us.
Right?
[Qiutian Pavilion]
I can't believe the immortal
looked like you.
That was an illusion created by the Moon Sword, right?
What you saw
was me.
Because I knew you were trapped in there too.
So I used our opposing power
to push you to your potential
and break through the illusion.
Weren't you afraid you'd strangle me to death?
I was.
Of course I was.
But I was more worried
we couldn't get through the spell
and die inside.
If you are still upset,
come on.
Pinch me.
Pinch you?
I don't want to.
I'm afraid to stain my hands.
If you dare to cheat me,
I'll pull out the Moon Sword
and stab you.
Lu Li.
Do you see?
She's destined to kill you.
Wait, I clearly saw
the Moon Sword devouring the God of the Sun.
Is there no problem
for Liu Shao to draw the sword?
Lu Li.
What are you thinking?
Nothing.
When are you going to draw the sword?
My Lord
let me refine the power of the King Herb tonight.
I'll go draw it tomorrow at noon
when the Qi of the Greatness is at its peak.
For your sake,
and my own sake,
I will pull out the Moon Sword.
Okay.
I have to go out of the mansion.
Wait for me to come back.
Remember.
Make sure you wait for me to come back before you draw the sword.
Do you understand?
It's such an important thing.
Of course I will wait for you.
What's wrong with Lu Li?
Why did the Moon Sword
let me see an immortal looking like Lu Li?
Master.
Liu Shao has passed the ultimate trial of Marquis Wuyang's Mansion.
I believe she can pull out the Moon Sword.
Very well.
I came back to ask you for advice.
Will it be dangerous
for Liu Shao to draw the sword?
Moon Sword is left behind by the gods.
How could it be dangerous?
Then do you know
what the ultimate trial of the Moon Sword is?
It's just a trial of a sword.
Without the master's control,
it's nothing more than
a false
and confusing illusion.
But the illusion
is just like a dream.
It comes either from one's own memory
or from the memory of the sword.
In my vision,
Liu Shao killed me with the Moon Sword.
But she suffered a backlash.
It's a sword from ten thousand years ago.
How could it have memories of you two?
So
in the illusion,
we thought they were us,
but it was an illusion created by the Moon Sword
with the memories of the two gods,
which was not entirely real?
But there is one thing that can't be wrong.
If even the God of the Sun
was once devoured by the Moon Sword,
what about Liu Shao?
Will Liu Shao be in danger?
As long as she doesn't use her vitality,
she'll be safe from the devouring.
Liu Shao wants to pull out the Moon Sword.
How can she not use her vitality?
Master, do you have any more…
Master.
Master! Master!
Ma…
Master, I only found this in his room.
Go on.
Yes.
If only one of you can live,
I will choose my disciple.
Remember.
Make sure you wait for me to come back before you draw the sword.
Do you understand?
Lu Li is not back yet.
I want to draw the Moon Sword.
Okay.
I'll help you.
Liu Shao.
In fact, there is another reason why I want to draw the Moon Sword.
I want to find out my origin.
You want the Moon Sword so badly.
Why haven't you returned then?
Do you think he's really being nice to you?
He just wants you
to help him pull out the Moon Sword.
Our master is both Lu Sheng.
Liu Shao.
So he didn't tell you?
It seems he's been hiding a lot of things
from you.
Is he hiding something from me?
Brother didn't come back
I didn't see him all night last night.
How come?
It's such a big deal for Liu Shao to draw the sword.
How can he disappear at this time?
I have a vague feeling
that something is wrong with Lu Li.
I'll go look for him again.
I'll go with you.
Let's go.
I'm leaving.
There are many things Lu Li didn't tell you.
Don't worry.
We just need to endure one more day.
Everything I've done is for today.
After she gets the Moon Sword,
I'll never care about that woman again.
I know.
You and I are childhood friends.
Liu Shao can't compare with that.
It's just
that you've worked so hard
to win her dependence.
After she pulled out the Moon Sword,
I'll show up and take it away.
And then charge her with collusion with the demon world
and intend to rebel. How about that?
Lu Li.
Where is Lu Li?
Are you playing some kind of trick again
and having someone pretend to be him?
What Lu Li?
Where is he?
You know him so well.
How could I find someone to pretend to be him?
Then where…
This is Lu Li's money bag.
Lu Li!
Lu Li, come out!
Explain to me!
[Imperial Cosmo Hall]
I will
be outside the mansion
to guard you.
Thank you, my Lord.
Remember.
Make sure you wait for me to come back before you draw the sword.
Do you understand?
After she pulled out the Moon Sword,
I'll show up and take it away.
Lu Li.
Which one is real and which one is not?
I can't think about this.
I have to calm down.
First, pull out the Moon Sword.
Liu Shao.
Wait for me.
Liu Shao!
Don't draw your sword!
It's a seal.
The seal left by the God of the Sun.
But how do I break it?
Do I have to
use the vitality in my body?
Liu Shao!
No!
Put the sword down!
I've sealed the Moon Sword
here with my spirit today.
For thousands of years,
those who do not have my spirit
shall not touch it.
So
I'm the key to unlock the Seal of the Sun.
Put it down!
[Immortal Palace. Four Seasons Tablet]
The Sun Spirit has reappeared on earth.
I wonder
if it's a blessing or a curse.
What's going on today?
The sunlight is shining directly into the sea.
It has never been seen in a thousand years,
no, in a million years.
How can this happen?
This is
Glazed Fruit.
The Brahma tree can actually break through the limiting demon world
and bear the Glazed Fruit that has the spiritual energy of heaven and earth.
Your little fairy
really pulled out the Moon Sword?
Liu Shao.
It's devouring her.
I can't let Liu Shao hold the sword.
He just wants you
to help him pull out the Moon Sword.
Liu Shao.
Don't come any closer.
Are you here for the Moon Sword?
Give me the Moon Sword.
You can't withstand its devouring.
I can't?
But you can?
I'm sorry.
Actually...
Lu.
Congratulations.
You've got the Moon Sword.
Why are you here?
Did you forget?
You promised Master
that we'd return when we got the Moon Sword.
Now that you've completed your mission,
we can go back.
Bai Feng.
Please behave yourself.
What happens between me and Liu Shao
has nothing to do with you.
You've already got the sword.
Why are you still pretending?
Think about
how much I've suffered
due to this woman.
What are you talking about?
So you're just doing it for the Moon Sword, right?
Lu Li, you've been using me.
Don't listen to her…
How can you do this to me?
You made a vow under the Brahma tree before.
The millions of Water Hyacinths can prove it.
Liu Shao.
He just wants
the Moon Sword.
You are the only one who can unseal it.
That's why he treats you so well.
So…
I didn't.
The illusion in the Moon Sword was real.
You've been using me all along.
You've always hurt me.
I never wanted to hurt you.
Please don't make things difficult for him.
He doesn't need to hurt you himself.
Do you know
that you and the Moon Sword are spiritually incompatible?
Pulling out the Moon Sword
will cost your life.
Don't stir it up.
Liu Shao won't die.
I won't let her die.
Give me back the sword.
Liu Shao.
You can't touch the sword.
I didn't.
I never wanted to steal your sword.
Liu Shao.
Everything I've done is for today.
Once I get the Moon Sword,
I'll never care about that woman again.
I'll just show up and take the sword.
No.
Lu Li.
Go away.
She's done this to you.
Why do you care about her?
It's all because of you.
It's because of you that Lu Li did this to me.
Liu Shao.
Don't!
Liu Shao!
That's interesting.
Is she going to
bring the sword to Aquatic Demons?
Lu Li.
Liu Shao.
He Na.
I'm sorry.
You were the only one I thought of.
Don't worry.
It's going to be okay.
Liu Shao.
You have to
trust me.
He Na.
Take me away.
Liu Shao.
♫On rainy days, the wind blows smoke♫
♫Into circles♫
Okay.
♫On both sides, I'm chanting♫
♫The night is sleepless♫
♫The shadows of the moon are incomplete, and people are in love♫
♫A cocoon of shadows♫
♫Your promise, my fate♫
♫I look at my love and send it to the clouds outside the garden♫
♫Looking at your ageless face at the end of the world♫
♫You put the winter snow in your ears and can't hear it♫
Lu Li.
♫When the flowers stop falling, you and I will miss each other♫
♫Everything in the world passes before understanding♫
♫After the missing, my face is still young♫
♫The day the flowers fall in the garden, the day we meet♫
♫If you see me for the first time in this life, I'll forever hold it in my heart♫
What's going on?
Where is the Moon Sword?
Where's Liu Shao?
Where's the Moon Sword?
Get the men together now.
We must find Lu Li and Liu Shao.
Apart from everything else,
we can't let the Moon Sword
fall into the hands of evil people.
Yes.
♫I look at my love and send it to the clouds outside the garden♫
Everything I've done is for today.
♫Looking back at the love that still remains in your past life♫
After she gets the Moon Sword,
I'll never care about that woman again.
♫You put the winter snow in your ears and can't hear it♫
Are you here for the Moon Sword?
I'm here to get the Moon Sword.
Don't.
Don't take my Moon Sword.
♫When the flowers fall, you and I will miss each other♫
Don't.
Liu Shao.
Don't be afraid.
I'm here.
♫Everything in the world passes before understanding♫
No one will take it from you.
Lu Li.
♫After the missing, my face is still young♫
Don't steal my Moon Sword.
Liu Shao.
It's me, He Na.
♫The day the flowers fall in the garden, the day we meet♫
Lu Li.
♫ The year of my life fleets♫
♫Whose year is it♫
Lu Li.
You're going to look for Liu Shao again?
I won't allow you to go to her.
You can't even protect yourself.
Come back with me to see Master.
Otherwise, if you lose the Moon Sword,
you and Liu Shao won't be able to get away with it.
I'll take you away to avoid the storm.
Even if you find her, what can you do?
Will she give you the sword? Will she?
What happens between me and her
is none of your business.
It's none of my business?
What do you mean, it's none of my business?
You should know
my feelings for you, right?
Your feelings
are none of my business.
But if you hurt Liu Shao,
then it's my business.
I won't forgive you.
Do you like her that much?
Yes, I do.
Unfortunately,
you're not meant to be together.
The Soul-Devouring Spell will kill you.
And the Moon Sword will kill her.
Just listen to me.
I'm doing this for your good.
The Moon Sword?
The spiritual power of the Moon Sword
is actually devouring Liu Shao.
Their spiritual powers are mutually exclusive.
This is not a simple weapon backlash.
Liu Shao's spiritual power is so special.
But why was she able to pull out the Moon Sword instead?
The Moon Sword will kill Liu Shao.
So you knew all along.
This is unfair to Liu Shao.
Liu Shao has suffered so much
all because she helped me pull out the sword.
I'm going to ask Master
what he wants to do.
So what if you go?
Liu Shao won't forgive you.
Because she saw
me conspiring with you to kill her, right?
Bai Feng.
You planned so carefully,
hoping Liu Shao to take me wrong.
But what did she see?
What she saw was the real you.
But was what she saw
the real me?
You really disappoint me.
Immortal Master.
The Moon Sword had been pulled out by Liu Shao.
But then
she went missing
with another disciple, Lu Li.
There's no news of their whereabouts.
I have sent many people to look for her
and found
it seemed
to be related to the demon world.
The Moon Sword has been unsealed.
The feud it involves
is beyond our control.
Ignore it for now.
Let's wait.
Wait?
Wait for what?
Wait for a god who can control it.
Yes.
But I thought it's been 10,000 years
since a God has been born in Immortal Palace.
Immortal Luo Ge,
disciple of the Immortal Master Wanwu,
is said to be gifted
who has the potential to become a God.
Now, he's in seclusion
striving for the status of Immortal.
So it seems
Luo Ge should soon be able to become an Immortal
and dominate the Immortal Palace.
Liu Shao is just a mortal woman.
But she is devoured by the God of Moonlight's Moon Sword,
and still unaffected by the Melody Flute.
Liu Shao.
How many secrets are hidden in your body?
There is nothing I can do
with the devouring of God's weapon.
This is all
I can do for you.
Is Liu Shao
really hopeless?
At least there is no way to save her
with the power of the demon world.
In that case,
I'm relieved.
General Fu.
What do you mean by that?
My brother seems to have an interest in her.
He always wastes his time on her.
I'm tired of seeing her.
Although I don't like her,
I can use
the Moon Sword she has.
Since the Moon Sword is in our world,
it'll help with my next plan.